G Dhananjaya 🔘 Featured

Systems Analyst, Data Analyst seeking roles in Software Development, Statistcs, Data Analysis, Machine Learning, Technical Analysis, Jenkins, Python, Panda, SQL, PLSQL



Current Designation: Data Scientist Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: MKS Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Data Analyst, System Analysis, Requirement Gathering, Data Analysis, Machine

Learning, Jenkins, Python, Panda, SQL, PLSQL, Statistics, Data Science, Predictive Modeling, Logistic Regression, Statistical

Modeling

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

6.5 years experienced Oracle SQL / PLSQL Developer with additional experience of Data analytics and ETL. Secondary skilled domains are Machine learning and Web application creation using ADF Oracle. Worked on domains like Manufacturing, Health insurance and Oracle Retail.

Work Experience

MKS as Data Scientist Dec 2020 to Till Date

DAta scientist into Supply chain Analytics using Python, Tableau , SQL and Machine learning

GAP IT Services India as Data Analyst

Mar 2018 to Nov 2020

Data Analyst Into Retail Operations using BI Publisher, SQL and Machine learning.

Cognizant as Program Analyst

Aug 2016 to Mar 2018

AMFC and BSC are American Healthcare providers which are using Cognizant's own product called Facets which is widely used in Healthcare industry

Client: BSC and AMFC

Project 1 and 2: Facets Database Designer

- Interface Development using PLSQL and Data stage.
- * Conceptual Design and Technical design.
- * PLSQL Development and work with ETL Developers.
- Performance and Unit testing once Interface development is done.
- * Facets Back-end Operations.

Tech Mahindra as Software Engineer

Mar 2014 to Jul 2016

TE Connectivity Data warehouse is maintained by a our team which provides technical Support and Development Client: TE Connectivity

Project 1: TED

- Technical Support and Development.
- Creation of database objects like tables, views, Procedures, Functions using oracle tools like SQL Developer.
- Involved in data loading using PL/SQL and SQL*Loader calling UNIX Scripts to download and manipulate files.
- Analysed and modified Packages to fetch complex data from different tables in remote databases using joins, sub queries and database links.
- Extensively used the advanced features of PL/SQL like Record, BULK COLLECT and VARRAYS.
- Debugging job failures and worked on RCA.

Key Contributions

- Automated few processes which was needed manual work which requires 1 hr effort every day.
- Worked as Developer, Support Analyst and Incident Manager.

Education

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from VIGNANA SUDHA DEGREE COLLEGE in 2010

PG: MCA (Computers) from Sri Venkateswara college of engineering and technology in 2013

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
Oracle 12c, SQL, PLSQL		
Reporting Tool BI Publisher		
ETL Data stage, Advanced PLSQL		
Oracle ADF and Oracle Retail		
SQL Programming		
Python		
Git, Jenkins, Kubernetes, Serena Dimensi		
Oracle ADF		

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time